When real life sucks, REEL life rules!
The 4:30 Movie is a comedy, romance film directed by Kevin Smith.
In the summer of 1986, three sixteen year old friends spend their
Saturdays sneaking into movies at the local multiplex.
But when one of the guys also invites the girl of his dreams to see the
latest comedy, each of the teens learn more about life and love.
Melody Barnegat, played by Siena Agudong.
Brian David, played by Austin Zajur.
Burny, played by Nicholas Cirillo.
Belly, played by Reed Northrup.
Manager Mike, played by Ken Jeong.
Major Murder, played by Sam Richardson.
The 4:30 Movie is a 2024 American semi-autobiographical
coming-of-age comedy film written and directed by Kevin Smith.
It stars Austin Zajur, Nicholas Cirillo, Reed
Northrup, Siena Agudong, and Ken Jeong.
The story is loosely based on Smith's experiences sneaking into movie
theaters as a teenager and his earliest romantic endeavors.
It was released on September 13, 2024, by Saban Films.
The film explores themes of coming of age, teenage
crush, semi autobiographical, movie theater.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.